export const quizData = [
  {
    category: 'Basketball',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'A free throw is worth how many points?',
        questionId: 1,
        answer: 1,
        options: [
          {
            option: 1,
          },
          {
            option: 2,
          },
          {
            option: 3,
          },
          {
            option: 4,
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the highest governing body of basketball?',
        questionId: 2,
        answer: 'NBA',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'BCCI',
          },
          {
            option: 'FIBA',
          },
          {
            option: 'PCI',
          },
          {
            option: 'NBA',
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these basketball players retired from the NBA with the highest career scoring average?',
        questionId: 3,
        answer: 'Michael Jordan',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Oscar Robertson',
          },
          {
            option: 'Michael Jordan',
          },
          {
            option: 'Wilt Chamberlain',
          },
          {
            option: 'Kareem Abdul-Jabbar',
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is the only player to score 100 points in a single NBA game?',
        questionId: 4,
        answer: 'Wilt Chamberlain',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Wilt Chamberlain',
          },
          {
            option: 'Kareem Abdul-Jabbar',
          },
          {
            option: 'Michael Jordan',
          },
          {
            option: 'Magic Johnson',
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question: ' Physical contact between two players is what kind of foul?',
        questionId: 5,
        answer: 'Personal foul',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Personal foul',
          },
          {
            option: 'Flagrant foul',
          },
          {
            option: 'Technical foul',
          },
          {
            option: 'Glitch foul',
          },
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: 'Cricket',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'In which year was the first ICC Women’s World Cup held?',
        questionId: 1,
        answer: 1973,
        options: [
          {
            option: 1970,
          },
          {
            option: 1971,
          },
          {
            option: 1972,
          },
          {
            option: 1973,
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'In which year did Kane become the ODI captain for the first time?',
        questionId: 2,
        answer: 2012,
        options: [
          {
            option: 2011,
          },
          {
            option: 2012,
          },
          {
            option: 2013,
          },
          {
            option: 2014,
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who holds the record for bowling the longest over in an international game?',
        questionId: 3,
        answer: 'Mohammad Sami',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Curtly Ambrose',
          },
          {
            option: 'Ashok Dinda',
          },
          {
            option: 'Mohammad Sami',
          },
          {
            option: 'Dragon Egg',
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which team will be making its ICC Women’s World Cup debut in the 2022 edition?',
        questionId: 4,
        answer: 'Bangladesh',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Bangladesh',
          },
          {
            option: 'Sri Lanka',
          },
          {
            option: 'New-Zealand',
          },
          {
            option: 'Australia',
          },
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is the only bowler to have conceded 90 or more runs twice in a World Cup ODI?',
        questionId: 5,
        answer: 'Kevin O Brien',
        options: [
          {
            option: 'Andre Russell',
          },
          {
            option: 'Kevin O Brien',
          },
          {
            option: 'Rashid Khan',
          },
          {
            option: 'Javagal Srinath',
          },
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
];
